basicjokes.com 2010-12-06

# Privacy Policy for 21st Century Basics Sites

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This privacy policy covers and is consistant among all the sites in the 21st Century Basics network which currently are Basic Jokes, Basic Music, Basic Quotations, Basic Inspiration, Basic Celebrations, Basic Famous People, Basic Bible Tools, Basic Eating, Basic History Online, and, of course, 21st Century Basics. 

21st Century Basics produced this privacy policy in an effort to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of the Basics 4 Life Website Network. 

21st Century Basics believes in all Internet users' rights to privacy. Basics 4 Life does not engage in any form of distribution or sale of Personally Identifiable information to third parties for their own promotional use, including but not limited to, names, email/postal addresses, and phone numbers. All information collected by the Basics 4 Life Website Network is not personally identifiable as it relates to consumers, nor does 21st Century Basics engage in any form of consumer profiling. 

**Advertisers**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org . 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Our advertising networks use cookies for the purposes of tracking when an Internet user has seen an advertisement. These cookies do not and will not provide our advertisers with any Personally Identifiable information. Instead, these cookies are used to inform the ad network if an advertisement has been served to the same computer before, and if so, when the advertisement was served. 

We use both session and persistent cookies on our websites. These are needed for site navigation and aggregate analysis of what is viewed on our site. 

**Opt-Out**

Internet users have the option to block the use of cookies by changing an Internet browser setting. In addition, users have the option to block the use of JavaScript, which is used by the Basics 4 Life Website Network to display advertisements. For more information, please see the documentation regarding your Internet browser. 

**Collection and Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Information collected by advertisers on their websites may contain Personally Identifiable information. However, data such as this is provided by the individual Internet user in the form of online order forms, contests, or otherwise through the advertiser website, not Basics 4 Life. This Personally Identifiable information collected outside the Basics 4 Life Website Network is subject to the privacy policies of the individual advertisers involved. 

**Links to other Sites**

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

21st Century Basics may find it necessary to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, any modifications made to this Privacy Policy will not materially affect the privacy of data collected by 21st Century Basics prior to the effective date of the policy change.
